All right, let's go.
Some good old paracetamol and ibuprofen.
Now, I'm gonna get in there and quickly get out.
Ha ha, smooth.
Smooth operator.
Oh, look at this here!
Oh, never mind.
I thought SEMA was transforming toxic sludge into more SEMA.
I was mistaken.
Okay, that looked better at first glance than it actually is.
Freezing Ace is sick, but only if you have unlimited spells.
Then it's really good.
Okay,
there's a wand here.
That's a nice little healing for me.
At this point, I may as well carry this around.
I don't think I'm gonna use those energy orbs because there are triggers on them.
It's too expensive.
What?
Oh,
what's that?
Oh, it's a Kiva skeevie.
Look, it's not even igniting this SEMA here.
Whoop!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I saw that one coming.
Let's heal some more.
Wait, is this some new music?
I don't think I've heard this track.
And you know what, having greed right now is not the worst thing in the world.
Money is big.
He had a wand too.
Oh, there's explosives underneath here.
Let's just get rid of that.
I'm It's healing down the road.
So
many liquids.
This game is a liquid simulator.
Get me to the SEMA.
What?
How?
Come on.
Ah, that's annoying.
Get in here.
Gotta shoot this again.
Just keep myself topped.
Ground to sand.
Not a bad wand, per se.
It does have a lot of recharge time.
Let me actually break the idea that I have in mind.
I am just so happy that this SEMA isn't actually explosive or flammable because that would have made my life so much harder.
Whoa.
Wow.
I'm gonna get in, get out.
There we go.
No, no, no.
Wrong balance.
And now I'm not... Fuck!
There we go.
Lost a lot of HP.
Show me more wands.
Actually, there's a... the drill is there and there's a bunch of gold.
I'm gonna get it.
Does this also count double when I pick this up?
I wonder.
It says per nugget.
I'm not so sure.
It's more like gold dust, isn't it?
Chaotic Polymorphine is not for me.
Purifying powder.
Did I fire that?
I didn't!
Yay!
Good old healing.
Thanks.
Kivoskivi.
I need hearts!
It's the big thing I need.
That is the only real thing that's stopping me from going to Yalkemisti.
Oh, hold on.
He's coming after me.
I see you there.
Get obliterated.
At least they're drowning in alcohol when they die.
Projectile gravity field.
Recoil.
Accelerating shot.
You know what?
That would be great with my black hole.
Yes!
That one I'm intrigued by.
I will get it.
Maybe get rid of this.
Projectiles caught within the field are attracted towards its center.
Oh, that's gonna be big if we ever find a healing spell.
Now, I'm gonna get up here.
Let's be careful.
Where exactly is this thing?
I gave it a shave.
Just a shave.
So, Seema's in here now.
Look at the eye, dude.
Let's go find some teleportation.
Especially because blood is kinda ripped.
Don't go in there.
Don't go in there either.
Stay back.
I'm just thinking of some stupid jokes.
Kill them all.
Love it.
My game is slowing down a little bit.
Oh no.
Okay, we're fine.
That is a lot of blood, right?
A lot of people died there.
A lot of good people.
Died in the massacre of 84, where an unknown sorcerer entered our home and just started murdering everyone in cold blood.
He brought him MG42 and he went to town.
No mercy.
Those were some dark days, man.
All we wanted was to hang out, have some beers, you know, do a bit of digging for some gold.
And then this guy shows up and just fucks us up.
Man.
Ruined a whole generation.
Invisiblium.
Now that wand up there, I do not believe I have used it because it's rotating.
Nevermind, this is also rotating.
Healing, healing.
Nice.
This actually does damage.
But nope.
I will take this back for now.
That was a bit risky.
What a combo.
All right, I'm going back up.
You know what the great part about Oh no, my, no, my.
I had a really dumb thump thought right now.
I almost shared it, but I stopped myself before doing it.
I'm proud of myself.
Oh,
I love appearing out of nowhere and just shooting.
Like they have no chance to react.
Just insta-death.
And imagine if we find a Tinka with wands everywhere.
That would make me feel very good.
Let's just say that.
Okay.
I'm, I don't have any more liquids.
I'm out of liquids.
I'm actually getting a little bit over eager here.
No, don't, don't go.
The flammoxium is flammoxing my brain.
Calm down.
Look at how fast that goes.
That's going through snow.
Unfortunately, no broken wand.
Man, my game is stuttery.
I feel like it's not like slowing down in the usual sense.
It just feels like it has frame time issues.
That makes any sense to you.
It almost feels like every fourth frame is skipped in a weird way.
I want that gold.
I gotta find a couple more wands to heal.
I do have a good amount of money for the next holy mountain.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
That guy has a wand.
Or does he?
No, no, no.
He doesn't.
It's the machine here.
Damn.
He took a lot of my HP.
Get out of there.
Shit.
No, no.
I'm close to dying here.
Where are all the wands at?
Maybe his charms will just go through the portal.
We quickly heal.
We fight off the dude.
Oh, no, wait.
Enraged.
Oh, no.
Wait a minute.
It's the big dude now.
And there's a heart.
Give me some of this SEMA.
I need SEMA.
Come on.
There we go.
Okay.
Let's think.
How do we do this?
Also, that wand is empty.
I emptied that.
This one, maybe?
I'm stuck.
I did not do that one.
It makes any hard, solid materials within a projectile's range turn into sand.
That sounds scary AF, but sure.
Oh, I see.
Oh, yeah.
That does work.
Damn.
This is a solid digging wand.
Although this only has a certain amount of uses, so there's that.
That's the healing I get from that.
There's another wand here.
Did I empty that?
I did not, but this one is kind of sketchy.
It casts two spells, so it could cast a summon large explosive box followed by a freezing gaze and then just fuck me up.
I'm not going to do it.
I don't trust that at all.
Nope.
Not happening.
That one I emptied.
There's a dude in here.
Hand over your lunch money.
Do I have pheromone?
So is there pheromone anywhere?
Because that would be a surefire way to get some healing.
He's even locked in here.
Look at this.
This is the ideal spot.
Let's see if we can't find some.
I mean, I guess I would have seen it by now if I did find it.
Almost feels like there's no liquids in this world except toxic sludge and sema.
Everything else has gone away.
I wonder if I can trick him into shooting me somehow without the pheromone.
He would have to be aiming at his friends.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Fuck, come on.
All my hard work is removed in an instant there.
There were some explosives hiding in there.
Did I actually clear this entire place?
It's almost unbelievable.
Okay, so let's just go through.
We're gonna grab the health.
Worst case, I can black hole my way out of there and and peace out, right?
Worst case, I could also try to see of acid.
No, wait, acid is not acid anymore.
Never mind.
Uh, let's see.
I could try an electric charge on this.
Maybe that's gonna work.
Hold on.
I'm not gonna be able to get through a shield.
This dude has like three layers of shields.
If I don't, if I'm not mistaken, that that dude is wild.
He'd be wilding.
We need the chain bolt.
We need to go back to the chain bolt.
This is it.
We go back to chain bolt.
I put in electric charge to make him get stunned.
If he's even able to get stunned.
So I change out this with that and I change out.
I could also give him... increases projectiles damage based on the number of creatures.
So not like the strength of creatures.
I mean, I guess I could just hot swap it real quick.
Let's see here.
Also, how much does that add?
Oh, that adds a lot of cast delay.
That's actually gonna be super slow.
Maybe I try this first and if it looks hopeless, I quickly hot swap it back and... in any case, I'm gonna black hole an escape path, so I have a quick way out.
Or maybe even better, I black hole not entirely way through, but some of it so I can teleport through the rest and he can't follow me.
How about them apples?
That seems good to me.
Other than that, maybe circle of stillness actually.
Maybe we throw in a circle of stillness.
Maybe, yeah, maybe we do that.
Circle of stillness.
But I would have to get rid of all of these really quick.
Let's do it.
Halfway through.
Beautiful.
I'm even gonna make...
Oh, here we go, here we go, here we go.
Here we fucking go.
Just take this, I don't even care.
How spells do we have?
Another black hole.
Is it the big dude?
It is, it is.
Okay, it's not entirely hopeless.
Oh, shit.
Yeah!
Motherfucker!
You ain't got nothing on me, bro!
That's amazing!
Wow.
That's a big one.
Super good.
You currently held one, loses half its capacity, but gains... nah.
I am tempted on this one, but it's just not very effective right now.
So, oh, you know what I'm gonna do then?
Watch this.
We're gonna...
Ah, fuck!
I'm planning for the future here.
No, wait, wait.
I don't want to re-roll this.
I want to keep this.
Back.
Abort, abort, abort.
I'm coming back to grab this later when I have more health.
But I guess it wouldn't be a bad idea to do...
if I re-roll somewhere else.
Put it back.
Just do it anyway.
Do it anyway.
I changed my mind.
I'm trying to understand exactly how this works.
All right.
Quickly switch it back.
Get this somewhere here.
There.
I also forgot I had this out down here, by the way.
I was supposed to use that against them, but I forgot about it.
Uh, okay.
I was in the moment.
So basically the plan now is to keep going.
Hopefully find some more health.
And if I...
So when I get to the next holy mountain and I re-roll there if I do, this one won't be affected if I end up changing my mind in the future about not getting this.
You know, maybe I'll... maybe I don't want to get it.
Who knows?
I also do wonder...
No.
If I re-roll in the next holy mountain, it's not going to affect these.
It's only the associated prick re-roll that actually affects the... Also, look at this.
There's text right here, too.
Unfortunately, I destroyed the first part of that text.
Let's translate it.
Let's take a break and translate that.
So the first two I recognize because that is indeed an E.
Uh, let me take my pen.
Let me just clean this up a little bit.
Put this there for now.
You can go over here.
Let's see here.
So EE I can probably fill in the first letter later.
Then we have the F and the F was a weird, um...
The F was not an F, but it was actually the R.
I think.
So it was an H.
And then we have the D, which is a T.
Oh, no, it doesn't look good.
Now we get the...
No, wait, this is the... Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's not H.
This is definitely T.
So if it's not H, it's...
Also, I need the music so I don't forget.
There we go.
We need to put on...
E.
I don't have E.
Or do I?
Is it lowercase?
The closest I have is that.
But that is not...
Okay, let's just ignore that for now.
And keep going.
Maybe we can fill in the rest later.
Then we have two more E's.
What the fuck could this word be?
E, E, and then we have the weird inverted seven, which is an N.
And then an actual seven, which is a D.
What?
Pretend.
Key.
Me.
Hold on.
Let me see it again.
E, E, F.
F, F.
I don't have an F.
What is the closest thing?
Man, I...
I'm really missing some things here, it seems.
No, but here's the thing.
The symbols we see in the game right now...
They are very different from the symbols on the actual tablet.
They're like weirdly condensed versions of them.
So we're gonna have to guess a little bit here.
So the F could be...
Feet.
No, it's not feet.
Uh, maybe it's...
Lead.
Seat.
Meat.
Hold on, how many letters do we have?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
We're missing three letters.
Uh...
Three letters.
D is a T.
What could this be?
I wonder.
Leaned.
Sent.
Ment.
Lent.
I'm missing some crucial information here.
Wait a minute.
Let's just go through here.
Beat, seat, deed.
Heat.
Meat, need, need, maybe.
Because the end does kind of look a little bit like that.
You know, it's kind of close.
Actually, we can't see the first one.
So that should be here, I guess.
But I don't recognize a word like that.
Pint, reent.
Scene, teent.
Vete.
Meat.
No, but there needs to be something here.
Discrete.
I don't know.
Okay, let's leave it like that.
We're gonna come back when we have another tablet, so we can fill out what we're missing from our alphabet.
We don't have enough.
We need more.
More!
Okay.
Now.
We move on, I guess.
But wait.
Matter eater sounds cool as hell.
That is the vacuum bounce.
Remind me of what that is?
Makes a projectile remove earth as it bounces.
Really?
And there's only 20 of it.
Okay.
Hold on now.
Don't use that.
I think I want to get another black hole.
Let's put some light on this.
And get that and put it here.
May as well do it.
No reason not to.
Whoops.
Okay, they were ready.
Oh, wait, I have I have trigger finger.
Oh, shit.
Oh, but if I put on...
I can just unequip my wand.
Why did I never think about that?
Also, another thing I noticed, it said spells can hurt you.
Oh, would you look at this here now?
Yoink!
I'm bringing that up immediately.
I'm bringing that up at the next board meeting.
Which is right freaking now.
And since the gods are already piss angry at me.
I don't mind using a bit of acceleration here.
I'm lazy.
I don't want to... Am I that lazy?
I am that lazy.
I unleashed something there.
What was I here for?
I just thought about it.
Wait.
Why did I just go back?
It completely escaped my mind.
Fuck.
Wait a minute.
Why did I just go back?
Uh...
Hold on, let me retrace my steps.
Wait, wait a minute.
Why did I just go back?
I just I thought about this.
I went down here.
I picked this up.
Oh, yeah, the broken wand.
That's right.
Broken wand.
That's true.
Let's go.
I'm a little bit tipsy.
Okay, that's that's my excuse there.
Just a tiny bit.
Okay, throw that on there.
The gig of death cross.
Well, well, well.
No.
Not in a million years.
Keep your shit.
That was bad.
Quick!
Get to the something.
There.
Okay, I lost a lot of hp just now.
Unfortunate.
Now I take this back.
Thank you very much.
What is that?
Oh.
It's steam.
It looked like some kind of metal object.
Did it not?
I was totally bamboozled just now.
Money.
Hand it over.
What is he doing here?
He must have escaped the uh...
collapsed hemisphere.
Still got a plate safe here.
No rushing in and...
going gung-ho here.
Giant magic missile and essence to power with a quadruple.
It is... Oh, dude.
This is a solid wand.
I like that wand.
I'm sorry, uh, freezing field or whatever.
I'm really sorry.
But that's gonna become my new main go-to wand.
And we can use it to heal a little bit.
Shit.
I ran out.
He's protected.
Also, this slime is really driving me nuts.
But we can't get high anymore to remove it.
The fungus has become something else.
I could try and kill the, uh, the big snake.
And we're right here, actually.
A dragon.
Uh, should we try?
I think we can do it.
Wake up.
Wake up, fool.
Gotcha.
Nice.
Even got some HP.
What do you got here for me?
Oh!
Oh, three spells per cast, though.
Gives a projectile energy field that constantly deals damage.
Nah.
I mean, the wand is kind of cool.
Good stats.
The only thing is three spells per cast, but maybe I can try and experiment with that, you know?
I'm gonna try it.
Also, can I heal with it right now, or is that too dangerous?
Modifier on this one and all of these.
The damage field makes me scared.
My life.
But wait, acid has become...
Uh, peat, I believe?
Pea soup or something?
Do it!
That looks scary.
That's nasty looking.
That can... Can that hurt me?
Okay.
Also, something fell down.
Fireball orbit.
That's right.
All right.
We did it.
Wait, what?
Huh?
Oh!
We can dig!
Because of the luminous drill.
I was about to say, this doesn't normally dig through this.
Okay, so basically what I want to try...
Also, I do have black holes, by the way.
I want to try going north.
I like how I say north and go that way.
East, north, and south of important places.
Hold on.
Let me check my map.
Unless I didn't fill it out.
I don't think I ever explored.
Basically, so far the tendency has to be that there's stuff...
somewhere around the cardinal directions of a highlight point.
So we're gonna go east, north, and south and experiment with that.
We start with east.
Since I already started.
Let's try and do this a little more pretty.
I can shoot infinitely.
I am tempted to throw on a...
If I throw on the accelerating shot on a black hole, that thing is gonna fly away to infinity.
But I'm too lazy to go back.
I'm simply that too lazy.
I can probably move faster here.
It doesn't look like there's anything this way.
It would be closer if any... No, actually that's not true.
Sometimes they hide things really far.
Hold on, is my triplet coat actually digging?
It's not, it's not, it's not, okay.
It's an optical illusion almost.
It's not the slowest.
It works.
Oh, what is this?
Wait, what?
I told you there would be something.
I just don't know what it is.
I knew it!
What am I looking at?
Okay.
So hold up.
A little further this way, we get to a...
Make this a little bit.
And it has like...
Platforms.
Wait,
is it supposed to be a face in the game?
Wait a minute.
One, two, three, four.
I'm gonna purify this later.
It's just, you know, something for now.
Standard.
I'm gonna do a little bit of this, a little bit of that.
I did it like this.
I did it like that.
And then it sort of...
No.
Switch to normal.
No line, please.
Sort of does a bit of...
Never mind.
Let's take it back.
This is fine.
So now we gotta explore here as well.
But let's start with the north and south of Dragon Cave.
Wasn't even that far actually.
I guess I was digging first.
Maybe it is worth to go back and upgrade my...
Put speed on them.
You know what?
Since I have this one as well.
Yeah.
Back to HQ.
We're gonna make a fast as fuck.
Uh, like hole.
And we're gonna have some fun.
I wonder what the purpose of that place is.
Like...
There's nothing there.
A bunch of platforms.
Very weird.
Nope.
Didn't mean to do that.
That was completely reactionary.
I don't know why I had that reaction to that flask.
Being like, shoot it!
But I did.
Okay.
Yeah!
Okay, so what I'm gonna do.
I want to try and make this wand work.
It does say spells per cast three.
That's a little bit...
You know.
But I'm gonna try.
Let's see if we can't try something new here that we've never done before.
We'll even leave some of these like lying a little bit scattered so I can pick them up later if I want.
Let's just see what happens if I naively throw everything on it.
Just like that.
What's gonna happen?
Wait.
So what's happening is it's pretty much doing the same thing except it's not double dipping because of the spells per cast being three.
So!
I can try to just throw on some more spells.
Just to satisfy that criteria.
Oh, actually just remove this.
One, two.
It should look for a third.
Hold on.
One spell.
Two spell.
Unless it doesn't work like that when the spells per cast is inherent.
On the wand.
Which is possible.
Let's try, um, throw on something like this.
Oh, I need to get rid of something.
I guess see if acid is useless now.
Let's become transformed.
Does it need another?
Oh wait, we need the double double double double double.
Let's wait.
Three spells.
One, two,
three.
We need another spell in front of the double.
Unless we, no, wait, wait, wait, we need, we need this.
Sort of.
Wait, one, two.
Let me think.
What if I just throw on a triple?
What then?
Spells per cast is three.
This is the first spell.
This is the second, which contains, let me just use two for make it simple.
This is the second, which contains one spell.
There's another spell in here that needs to be satisfied.
So we do that.
But then there's a third spell here that the wand is looking for.
But it's not there.
So it's gonna go back to the front and double dip, right?
It is not.
Okay, so it basically doesn't work.
Double dipping doesn't work like that when it's inherent on the wand.
So instead, what we're gonna do is we're gonna put something like this on to force this to look for something.
With that there.
So one spell, two spell, three spell, and this one has this one.
And no, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
We need an extra spell.
We need another one.
We need one more.
Uh, let me take another one of these.
This should work.
Yeah!
I mean, it's double dipping.
Look, it's double dipping, but I'm still running out of mana quite fast here.
I guess it's because of all the magic arrows.
So we got to remove those and replace them with something less mana intensive.
Fucking nailed it.
How about these?
That is 30 mana.
That's no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I guess I have a bunch at home.
Uh,
hold on.
Oh, oh, oh, wait, wait, wait, we also have this.
Wait, wait, wait, we have triggers.
We have triggers.
Hold, hold, hold the phone, hold the phone!
Let's try something wholly new.
Let's, uh...
Let's think.
Remove that.
It's gonna trigger two spells now on impact.
Let's say that one.
And this one.
What does that do?
Sweet.
Damage is decent, I guess.
What if we remove this?
Too slow.
But...
Can we utilize the heavy spread instead?
Not that we need it, I think, because this is already... no, it's just 10 mana.
It's breaking my brain a little bit.
This is also 15 mana.
If I could find a single... nah, you know what?
I don't know.
I'm gonna just stick to what I know here.
Let's stick to what I know for now.
I'm gonna experiment a little bit later.
Because what I need down here is some spells that don't cost that much mana.
Some dummy spells.
Like a chainsaw, for example.
Doesn't cost anything.
And what was I missing up here?
The double.
Let's just make sure I understand this.
That one.
Boop, boop, boop, boop.
Yeah.
That's what I had.
Let's keep this one here.
And then this wand, we can put this stuff in.
With the accelerating shot.
But it's gonna cast three spells per cast.
I don't want... that's the annoying part here.
I can only carry one of these if I want to do the thing I'm trying to do.
If I want to be super efficient.
But I guess three maybe enough and then for the rest I can use this up here if I want to.
And we also have this.
I mean, it's fine.
It's okay.
Put some light on that.
All right, let's go do the thing we intended to do.
I gotta explore.
Go where no man has ever gone.
And shine the light like a man has never shone before.
And kill things on the way.
What's that?
Boop, boop, boop, boop, boop.
I need to collect that.
Fuck, I shouldn't have broken it.
Shit.
Oops, I didn't mean to do that actually.
Get rid of it, get rid of it.
Okay, thank god.
Okay, let's try going up.
Oh, but I guess it does expire quite fast.
Oh, never mind.
It doesn't actually.
I hear something.
I think I hear something.
Wait, wait a minute.
Okay, I don't think there's anything that way.
That was quite a hole I made.
Compared to this one, it's nothing.
Actually, maybe it's the same.
I don't want to use all my holes though.
Let's do another one down.
And then I'm gonna use my first one to keep digging.
I want to make the hole at least a little nice.
I guess we're going at an angle then.
A little bit of an angle.
Hello!
What is this?
Oh wait, are we just in uh...
Actually, I'm not sure where we are.
Hold on, what comes after a jungle?
Are we in the vault right now?
Down here?
Is the vault bigger?
This looks like the vault actually.
It usually has a little uh, semi area.
Right?
With some mushrooms.
But notice this.
There are no mushrooms to consume.
They've all become vomit.
Ayy!
Nice.
Acceleration.
You know what?
I shall take that.
I don't even know if I should explore it.
I'm not even done with the jungle yet.
But I guess go... I could go check the um...
The perk reroll stuff now.
Since I'm here.
I wonder if uh...
Oh man, this is a nice check.
I do wonder if...
Big steward...
Is gonna be here if I come from the bottom.
And I never entered the portal.
Maybe going through the portal is what triggers the dudes.
When you've already angered them.
I don't know.
Let's find out.
It's a great test.
I need to go up.
Somewhere now I think is a good time.
Oh don't you shoot that at me!
Scary.
Ah!
You're not even dead.
I thought for sure I got you.
He's bleeding diamonds.
That's the same as always.
Nice.
Getting good money here.
Man, having the acid become something else is actually fantastic.
Really nice.
We're here!
Is he gonna be here?
Wait, I'm getting the music.
He's here for sure.
He's here, he's here.
Okay.
Let's uh...
Do this systematically here.
And smart.
I'm gonna make some entrances with black holes.
Oh.
There's this thing down here.
Oh don't touch that.
Sir, sir.
Maybe I can lure him out.
I'm way too slippery.
Oh!
It fell off!
That's hilarious.
I didn't know that could happen.
It's a work sack.
We're approximately...
That is...
a bunch of wands.
So it's like right over here I need to make a hole.
Gotta kill some fools.
Ha ha ha!
Shooting fish in a barrel.
Is that electricity going through there?
No, it's just a glinting of gold.
Bring it on, sister.
Oh my god!
You're nothing!
Incredible!
Wait, why is the music still playing?
Is there another one?
Did they send two of you now?
Okay, so watch.
We're gonna do this now.
We're gonna...
Hold on, something's going on.
There's another one.
Where are you?
No?
I'm being bamboozled by the music.
I don't...
I don't know.
Okay, so now this is here.
I don't want to use it.
But I just put it there, you know?
Hold on, is there someone above me here?
They 100% sent two.
I think the other one must have followed me.
And he's hiding somewhere.
Explosion immunity.
Um, I mean, that's obviously the one to take, I think.
There's no real question here.
Just take it.
Yep.
Yep, yep, yep.
Converts nearby non-magical liquids into explosive gunpowder.
That is a sick wand.
Actually...
Two spells per cast.
0.07, 0.20, 0.50.
Oh, but this one is way better though.
This is the way better wand.
But this one is not bad.
I think I want to buy this and replace...
one of my other shitty wands that I have.
Like that one.
It's time to replace some of the...
crap that I have, you know?
That one, for instance.
This is a great wand.
I wonder what happens if I do this now that blood has changed.
Well, I guess it's not technically blood, but still.
It's still blood mist.
Oh, is this the only way to get bloody now?
I wonder.
Because all the other blood is gone.
So that would be a way to...
gain that little...
chance of attaining critical hits.
By the way!
I just realized, with unlimited spells...
you could put this into your rotation up here in your main wand.
So that you always have blood on you and you will always have a higher chance of attaining crits.
That would be sick!
But you need unlimited spells.
I feel like this guy is trapped.
He's bugged inside a wall or something.
I don't understand what's going on.
This one can go back up here.
I think I just want to try and throw this on here and see what happens.
Yeah, so I still... I don't double dip right now.
I do not perform a double dip, but if I do...
that...
I still don't double dip.
I need something in between.
Is that cheap?
25.
Oh, I hate this music!
Stop!
Concentrated explosion.
That is actually not bad.
Adds more damage to the explosion.
If I can have something small that actually does an explosion, but not a big one...
Fireballs, maybe.
I'm not sure.
I wish I could understand what's going on here.
It's one spell.
It's kind of fun.
I need to double dip on it.
I was about to say, maybe we don't need the quick recharge now that the wand is better.
It's still a little bit slower here for sure.
You can see the recharge is triggering.
Oh my lord.
It's a mystery.
Am I double dipping on the luminous drill as well?
Hold on, what if I just do this?
Hold up a second here.
Oh no, we need a dummy of course.
But if I do this here, can I maybe double dip on the reduced recharge?
What if I put it up like this?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
See, that's interesting.
It's definitely faster like this.
No, it's not actually faster.
Ahh!
Annoying!
Hold on, I'm going to check real quick if this is a bug.
I don't like this music.
The music is just messing with me.
Cheers everybody.
Aha!
It was a bug.
Unless the guy is off somewhere.
I got to keep my eyes open though in case he actually is somewhere.
This is promising.
Put this on this one for now?
Just because I may want to replace this one.
Because this is my worst one right now.
Alright.
I do a lot of money.
I don't want to buy any of this though.
Is that crazy?
Let's move on.
Let's scout this entire place for...
Actually no, no, I wasn't done with the jungle.
Because there is probably a bunch of health.
That I haven't picked up there.
So I need to do that now.
Oh come on.
Beautiful.
Just double check.
Yep, works as expected.
Oh!
You scared me.
God damn spiders.
I nearly had a heart attack.
Oh no.
Remove the wand.
Let's just wait it out.
We got a wand in here.
Ha!
Explosive.
Magic bolt with trigger, huh?
Fireball thrower.
Ooh, mana charge speed though.
Whoa.
That is pretty sick.
Replace this one.
Not bad.
Maybe we can make something great with that digging wand.
Or even put my current stuff in there.
I'm basically here for hearts.
And then when I reach an acceptable amount of health, I'm gonna take the perk that gives me 50% more health and then I'm gonna go back up and fuck up Yalchimisti.
Because as soon as we do that, we're pretty much golden.
Because that means we can black hole a lot, which is a good start.
And we need to find some healing.
That's the next step.
Healing would be stellar.
Gum would be perfection.
Oh my gosh, calm down, calm down.
Who's doing that?
Yo, calm down.
Don't shoot that.
I can heal with that.
Look at him hiding.
Yeah, I'm so slow and sluggish, the slime.
Also, I gotta go back to that one room with all the platforms and look north, east and south.
I do wonder what the hell's going on with that place.
Okay,
so I'm here now.
Let's go west.
Not too far west though, because I know what awaits me.
Whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop.
Watch this.
Levitation.
Plasma beam orbit, huh?
Huh?
Let me see that for myself.
What that looks like.
Although, hold on.
These things are gonna jump, jump, jump, jump, jump, jump, all around.
I don't think I like that.
I'm scared of, no, you know...
I'm scared of this wand.
I don't know.
No, no, no, no, we're not gonna, nope.
Nope.
I'm too frickin' scared.
That's not gonna happen.
Okay, down we go.
Feels so weird to have fast levitation.
And you don't have acceleration.
Spark bolts.
That's actually important.
I need some of those.
They're like dummy spells.
I'm gonna take a couple.
So it's right here next to all the wands.
There it is.
Deposit a couple of these up here.
I don't even know about this, this is weird.
Maybe we remove this as well.
There, a couple of dummy spells.
That's actually not a bad wand.
Hold on.
Oh, mana charge speed, yikes!
Never mind, never mind.
It's horrible.
I was just about to throw all my primary spells on it.
Good thing I didn't.
What's this?
Aha!
Now we're talking.
I like that.
On this one, specifically.
Because look at the mana charge on it.
Not that it costs any mana, but it has very low castelay and all that.
Right, this one may be better, even.
One-thirteen.
I'm going back with that as well.
And that is a great dummy spell.
You need to die.
I've been a thorn in my side for too long.
Okay, so use this there.
We're gonna use, I think, this one.
.07 point, yeah, let's see here.
Because then we use, and I can probably just use this one for the teleport.
Nah, that's a waste.
Yeah, that's a waste.
It's only two slots.
That ain't good.
What was I doing?
Where's my heavy spread?
Ah, did I throw that away?
No way.
No, it's here, it's here, it's here.
Thankfully, I didn't throw it that far away.
There it is.
Beautiful.
Digging right there.
But this is also a great dummy spell for this thing up here.
So I'm gonna do my experiment now.
Before I do, let me grab the wand I left behind, because it may be important.
Put this here.
No, actually, that's fine.
But this is here for now.
I think I have all it takes to make something really, really neat.
Just down, down, down, this was not it.
Man, look at all this crap!
Vomit and SEMA.
Make the world drunk and make them vomit.
That's what I've done here.
Hide!
God damn!
Shit!
Okay, where was I?
Over here, doing something.
Was it more to the right or left?
What was over here?
There it is.
That made my heart jump!
Okay, okay, here we are.
All right.
Let's see now.
Let's have a look-see.
All right, the plan is to throw all of my spells in here and make it work down here, because this wand slaps.
It's kind of neat.
So just put some holes right here for now.
And then we're gonna make a digging wand.
The digging wand shall be...
I mean, this one is not a bad digging wand.
That is a digging wand right there in itself.
That's just straight up.
Works.
Could even put a light on it.
Okay, let's see here.
Down, down.
And then I maybe want to use this outside of digging, because this could be my...
If I can make my main damage wand a digging wand combined, that would free up a whole new wand for me, right?
So that would be a big deal.
So, this guy right here throws three spells per cast.
One spell.
Two spell.
And then he needs a three over here, so we need to fill it up with dummy.
One of them is gonna be a spark bolt there.
The other one is gonna be a digging bolt here.
Okay.
And we may have to swap this around, because it does have a recharge time reduction, so maybe this one is not even needed.
We'll have to see.
So, so far so good.
Now...
Instead of the luminous drill...
Wait.
Ah, so hold on.
These modifiers affect a bunch of spells, I guess.
Because spells per cast is three.
One.
Two.
Yeah, this one is gonna, no, this one's gonna affect that.
Oh, but hold on, this one does just castalate by a lot, so that may actually be the thing.
That is what's going on.
This is already a lot better.
If I put this here...
It's the same.
If I remove this...
Then it doesn't do what I wanted to.
Let me see the board.
No double dip.
Here comes the double dip.
You see?
There it is.
That's the dip.
By the dip.
So it's super good.
It's super good now.
If I can only, if I only had a chainsaw or another digging bowl that I could put right here so we don't add this extra five mana into the rotation.
Because I think that five mana may be what's draining my mana right now.
Look.
It does charge pretty quick and this is a decent one right now.
But you know...
Another thing...
Maybe the spark bolt is what we throw in now.
Instead of a double spell...
We're gonna do something like this.
One, two...
Oh my goodness.
Holy cannoli.
Wait.
Instead of 25 mana here...
Why is that so fast?
That feels like the audio can't even keep up here.
Oh my god.
Hmm.
What am I...
That costs 12.
This costs 10.
If I remove this...
Also, I gotta be testing the damage to see if I'm actually doing it.
Oh wait, this statue is gone.
Oh, it's probably gone over here as well.
Yeah, it's annihilated.
Fuck.
Dang it.
Well.
So this one does cost 15 now.
So if I can get rid of about 15-ish...
Actually more like...
What did this cost before that I had?
It was actually just a double spell.
What if I remove this?
Oh, that actually shoots pretty fast without it.
We don't even need it right now.
It is a bit violent though.
Are we double dipping?
We're not double dipping.
Okay, we're not double dipping.
So we need something in between.
That's one spell.
That's actually the second.
Two spell.
And that's blah blah.
And then we need an extra...
What about the light?
If we can double dip now, we're golden.
We add a...
Wait, wait, wait.
We add a double.
That's the answer to our prayers.
It's not the answer to our prayers.
Never mind.
We're not religious, I guess.
We need to believe more in the gods here.
Hold on.
So one spell.
Two spell and that's blah blah.
So the third... We need to throw an extra in.
It doesn't quite work the way I thought it would.
This is gonna throw that one and that one.
If only I had a spark bolt with a single trigger.
That's really what I need right now.
I think the answer may be a double here somehow.
So that's one spell, two spell.
But this already is two spells.
So in reality, it's one more and one more.
But in front.
There it is.
There it is, baby.
I fucking did it.
Now we're double dipping.
It's going down a little slower, but it is going down nuts.
It is going down because we're adding a bunch of extra spark bolts.
So the future for us is to find more digging bolts or chainsaws that we can put in here as dummy spells so that we don't use five mana.
Or of course, we find another add mana, which would be amazing.
And this way, we're not even using the reduced recharge time.
So that means we can use that somewhere else when we need to.
Very cool.
Very ne- or if we find a spark bolt with a single trigger, of course.
That would also do the job.
Now, I'm just assuming this is better damage than what I had before.
I don't know.
We'll have to see.
But I'm assuming it is.
This spark bolt carries with it a triplicate bolt and a digging bolt.
So that means we are actually digging at the impact.
So that means...
Oh, it would be nice to have a luminous drill on impact, though.
What if we change this?
No, that's- that's- no.
I mean, we can still dig close quarters, I guess.
But, uh, yeah.
All right, all right, all right, cool.
Let's- let's try that for a spell here.
And then...
We have freed up a wand from digging.
We can put whatever we want in there now.
Let's pick up some spells that we may need later.
Also, I completely forgot about this.
Oh, that's 40 mana drain, though.
That's too much.
Okay, grab an extra one of these.
How about that one?
I have too many of these triplicate thingies.
Let's get rid of that one.
And that one.
I don't like the electricity.
Just because I'm afraid of hurting myself.
This is good.
That is good.
Very nice.
I think I am good with this.
I'm happy.
Oh, hold on.
Black holes.
I felt like I missed something.
Oh, I put them here, I guess.
Put that there.
That's black hole.
And this is my- I don't even know what that- Maybe this will be my healing wand when I find healing.
Hopefully I find healing.
Okay, let's go.
Let's freaking go.
Let's find some hearts.
And test the damage here.
Let's just see.
Okay, it feels good.
It feels really good.
Really feels good.
Feels violent, which is what I like.
Violence is good.
Everyone knows it.
Solves all problems, at least in this game.
I would say the only downside compared to the earlier iteration of this wand is that...
I need to be a little more precise.
The other one was a little bit more...
...shoots it.
But this one does shoot further, so that's another thing.
All in all, this wand is way better.
Okay, I'm gonna go west again, because I didn't quite explore that place thoroughly.
Look at that wand.
Huh?
God damn, I'm doing damage.
And it's fast, and it's precise.
Let me see here.
Oh yeah, baby.
Things are dying.
And look, the digging.
It digs as well.
It's a good dick.
Ah, crap cake.
Hold on.
Expanding a slow projectile that increases its damage over time.
Double.
So this one, that one.
Yikes.
But it heals, so let's just see.
Heal me up.
Okay, that was less scary than I thought.
And then the black hole comes out.
I love the effect of the spells around the black hole.
Okay.
Thanks.
Do I want any of this, by the way?
The expanding sphere.
It does 75 damage.
Adds a bunch of cast delay.
This wand is kind of dope, though.
735 mana charge.
Maybe I can use that for whatever later.
But honestly, I already have good wands.
It's all about finding spells now.
I'm gonna keep this, I think.
Another wand.
Sweet.
Again.
Holy shit.
Increase lifetime.
Add mana!
Dude, increase lifetime for black holes?
Add mana for my wand.
We're rocking!
Fantastic.
No, no, no.
Get up.
Nice.
Also, there's a worm here.
Oh my god.
And single spark bolt with trigger?
Add mana?
Does it get better?
I'm coming back for these black holes.
Holy shit.
Are you kidding?
Why am I so lucky right now?
Ice ball.
You know what?
I'm gonna black hole a little path in there.
Not there, though.
This is really lazy of me.
Okay.
That works.
Do that.
Up here, up here.
Okay.
God damn, dude.
We have everything we need now.
This is just incredible.
And we need to have a reduced lifetime as well.
Not sure what I would use it for, but we have it.
I'm taking it.
Maybe we get rid of the rock.
No, keep the rock.
You never know.
Actually, maybe get rid of this one and take the three.
Maybe we can get rid of this one by now.
No, actually.
Well, we can be bold now.
Now that we have so much add mana.
We have to remember, it does add castile.
But that's what this is for.
This effectively nullifies an extra add mana.
Let's get rid of these.
Get rid of the double.
Here's the thing.
Oh, whoa.
This thing has an explosive effect on it.
Didn't we find something that increases explosion by 20?
Because that is essentially a damage plus times two.
Where did we find that?
Somewhere we had that.
That would be insane.
Maybe even this one.
Does we have so much mana now?
Are we double dipping both of these add manas?
I think we are.
Damn, we need more add mana.
There it is.
What the fuck?
What the fuck is going on?
Damn.
Wow.
But hold on.
This is 40 mana.
For 13 damage.
This is 15 mana for six.
And you know what?
This is essentially just the carrier.
I'm going to treat this as the carrier and we got to put some shit in here.
And I'm talking triple, baby.
And some other stuff.
Some other goodies.
Just fill it up with goodies.
Like that's already good, but we got to fill it up more.
We need some big boys.
We have so much mana now, maybe it is fine to just throw that on there.
That's super okay, yeah.
And remember, the damage plus is going to be added to all of these little...
dudes in there.
What is the craziest spell?
What if we put in a...
chain pulled in here?
Yo, that looks sick!
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
We got to conserve a mana a little bit now.
Ooh, that goes on fast.
And the thing is, we're not double dipping right now.
Let's see if we can double dip this.
And maybe we don't need all three then.
So, one, two...
one, two, three...
That looks insane.
So, one, two...
three, and this should be...
one, two, it should, it should, this should double dip.
One, two...
Hold on, hold on.
Is it double dipping?
Is it just so fast that I can't tell?
I don't think so.
Unless the double dip is so clean, that is actually essentially the same thing.
Know that I can't tell.
The double dip is happening, but I can't tell.
I guess that's possible.
But usually it's not that clean.
The double dip is always dirty.
If you double dip, it's dirty.
It's the DDD, the double dirty dip, you know?
From a distance.
If you put on a long distance cast, it would be the quadruple D.
The distance double dirty dip.
Very frowned upon in the community.
But I don't give a shit about that.
I do it anyway.
Um...
Yeah.
So, this is one, two, but that carries with it this.
So, actually...
I see what the problem is.
I was counting these into the three up here.
But it's wrong.
Because this is just a carrier of a...
Basically a payload.
And all of this is considered as one.
Right?
So, what we really need is... We actually still need a double spell.
Outside of here as well.
Basically this.
So, double... Okay, so, one...
Two...
This is gonna carry this shit.
Let me do this.
Uh...
And then the double is gonna...
One...
It's not quite there.
It's not quite there yet.
I mean, not that I need to put this in here.
I just...
You know, it would be fucking hilarious.
Because it looks fun.
I mean, it looks completely bonkers.
Um...
What if I put one here, actually?
So, hold
on.
This adds 90 mana every time I click the button.
90.
And that's almost all of this already.
This is like 80.
I think maybe...
If I was double dipping, I wouldn't go out.
I wouldn't be um.
Because there's no way I'm getting to 180 mana per recharge here.
There's no way I'm getting all that high up.
Like, this is five, you know?
This is zero.
No way, no way.
So, I think it's confirmed we're not double dipping.
Just by the math alone.
Yeah.
So, let's try and see if we can't force the double dip.
At least I've reached the conclusion now that we're not double dipping and it's just being masked as a non-double dip.
Even though it was DDing, you know?
One...
Two...
Wait a minute.
Two... and this contains this shit.
We need to get rid of the triple.
Actually.
Double this instead.
One...
Two...
So that's considered one.
Now we need one more.
This is not the one, I think.
No.
In fact, I think we need one more slot if I'm not crazy.
Let me just for argument's sake remove that.
And put in...
Okay, no, it's still not doing it then.
One...
Wrapping my head around the fact that we have three spells per cast and we're doing all of these doubles in here with a trigger is breaking my brain.
One, two...
This is one of them.
This is gonna carry the double here, which is this and that.
So I should get rid of that.
This is two and the three is up here.
So essentially, I think we need an extra double outside of here.
I don't have another double, but...
Unless I just light it up.
Oh, no, no, this is still the third, so we need to put a little dummy there.
No, I don't understand.
I think I'm getting tripped up here by the three spells per cast.
It's really breaking me.
I can't do it.
So you know what?
We do have a two spells per cast wand, which is also kind of dope.
How about we try it on that?
Let's put some stuff down here for now.
I think this one up here is getting a little nuts.
Do we even need the recharge?
I think we do.
Let's just do this for now.
So if this is two spells per cast now, so that would be one spell, two spell.
This one needs to carry a trigger.
And that trigger does its own thing.
It casts these two, and then there's another one.
The double dip is real!
You saw that?
Very hard to see, but it happened.
Oh, no, no, no, it happened because I was low mana, I think.
Never mind.
It wasn't happening.
I was imagining.
Okay, but you know what?
We don't need to throw in the chain bolts.
It's getting a little ridiculous anyway.
The chain bolt is totally over the top.
Fuck the chain bolt.
Let's just make it happen without it.
Let's remember what I did.
I did this one, double...
We could even put in a triple there, I guess.
Now we put in all kinds of goodies, and that goody doesn't have to be a chain bolt.
Fuck that.
No, no, no, no, no.
Actually, there.
It needs to go there.
Not there.
The light can go away.
So what else can we put in here?
And these are all going to be affected by damage plus.
So I think, keep it as simple as possible.
Honestly, just spark bolts.
Spark bolts are the way forward.
Although, this does do 10 damage, which is kind of a big difference.
I guess we've got to see how far we can push it without going in.
Okay, we're still owning.
We can probably put another one of these in there then.
Throw this away.
Triple one.
Oh, I can only do three, I guess.
So, remove that.
Oh, but hold on, the recoil here is way too nuts.
Look, I can basically fly forever.
I guess this one does add a lot of recoil.
The spark bolts do not.
That's the trade-off I have to make here.
If I do this instead.
Oh, much better.
Actually, it's not much better.
It is much better.
But the damage will suffer.
But maybe that's a fair trade to make for now.
I like this.
I do.
We could even put in a short range.
No, we can't.
That's too expensive.
Let's put increase lifetime on our black holes as well.
This is our thingy there.
Put the light on.
If we put increase lifetime on long distance cast, I wonder if we can go further.
Oh, wow.
Is it going so far it cannot actually teleport me?
Oh!
Oh, my gosh!
That's fantastic!
Damn!
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Also, wait a minute.
Maybe I just embraced the... Hold on, I can't get this out of my head.
I want to get mega damage.
Give me one more of these, please.
I just embraced the... No, no, no, I hate that.
I hate that so much.
That's terrible.
That is better.
I like that.
No more changing.
We're done.
Throw these away.
Put this one down there.
This one goes here.
Increase lifetime.
Stay here with the black holes that I'm going to put.
Where are my black holes?
Oh, I left them behind, didn't I?
This one right here is trash.
I'm going to leave this one here.
Go grab the other one.
If I had a quadruple here...
I guess we could double...
Nah, this is fine.
This is fine.
Maybe this is even too much.
Oh, yeah, it is!
We don't need that.
I just don't know if the double dip is happening here.
Does it matter at this point?
Like, that is already so good.
It is slower.
So we add another.
Two of them.
Did I just throw something away?
Is the dream alive?
I
kind of want to try this, guys.
No, I don't.
I lied.
I'm going to hate the wand because I go oom.
I'm going to hate it.
I just know it.
Let's go.
Also, I haven't found a heart in like a million years.
So where did I leave my black hole?
I think it was up here somewhere.
There.
Switch these around.
We're back.
The audio can't even keep up with how fast this wand is shooting.
Look how fast they die.
Oh, hello.
Jesus.
Wait, worm blood has become lava.
I think I have enough to kill the alchemist, you guys.
But of course, we got to find some healing.
Oh, there's a heart.
I'm painfully slow.
I take flight whenever I shoot.
And this is even the nonmassive recoil version of the wand that I made.
Hold on, I am...
No,
no.
Can I hurt you?
I don't know if I can hurt you.
It's always a crapshoot whether or not I can hurt you.
What's on this wand?
Null shot.
It causes a projectile to cast a copy of itself upon expiring.
Oh, yeah?
I don't know about this.
That one is kind of cool, but...
Come on, take out the fire.
But I'm going to shoot it a couple of times.
That should be okay, I think.
Yeah, we're okay.
Oh, no, I'm going to spawn a bunch of friendos.
Oh, my God.
Protectiles everywhere.
Now that...
I have a problem with.
That I will not pick up.
But hold on.
I am immune to explosions.
Fuck it.
Heal me.
Awesome.
Oh, God.
I've been here.
I healed with these already.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Be careful, be careful, they bleed lava.
I'm actually kind of scared.
I have to remember, when I go down there...
No, wait, I did already kill.
Big steward.
Down in the next area, didn't I?
I feel like I did.
No need to be afraid of him anymore.
I think we've cleaned this area well enough.
Let's just go through.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We've cleaned this.
Yep.
Yep, yep, yep.
Oh, no.
Get it off of me.
Should I heal?
Heal.
Better safe than sorry.
All right, let's check out this area then.
Fill up our HP a bit.
Then it's soon time to grab that HP buff.
Uh, electricity is still scary as fuck.
Really worry about it.
Uh-oh, that was close.
Whoo!
I won.
Uh, no thanks.
I'm okay.
Grab it!
Whew.
Oh, there was a bunch of electricity up here as well, I believe.
Yeah.
Man, I lost all of my HP.
Fuck me, dude.
We're in a bad shape.
We need wands.
Gotta play slow.
And fight wands.
Fuck!
I'm reeling.
Guys,
I'm gonna go up again.
I'm gonna go all the way up...
to the beginning.
There's gotta be wands I missed, and I'm playing it safe.
I could die here if I'm not careful.
So...
I gotta go up, man.
And I may also have left some healing behind.
I'm not sure I've taken all the healings.
In any case, there's gonna be healing in...
the hemisphere...
in the cave.
I could also take this now.
Will that actually heal me a little bit right now?
It will, okay.
Fuck it.
Alright, I'm going up.
We're going all the way up now.
I think I did shoot that one.
I did.
Oops.
Come on.
Did I take the healing here?
I did.
Hold on, there's a...
Say what now?
No!
Also put these in this.
Spiral arc.
Would I want that?
Maybe.
It's kind of cheap.
Let's just hang on to that.
That's the wand I had, right?
Oh, right!
This one!
Uh, you know what?
I'm taking this with me.
Yes!
Oh!
Chaotic path.
Wait a minute.
You also see something here.
Eleven and four explosive.
Thirty mana.
Whoops.
Hey!
That's kind of cool.
Can I afford another one?
Not really.
But...
kinda.
Let's do that.
That seems fun.
No!
No, no, I don't want to be... I don't want to be able to... I don't want to be able to spam it.
Yeah.
Even this one.
Oh, that's perfect.
That's perfect.
Okay.
Let's find some wands here.
Like that one.
Always casts...
Wait!
I'm immune to explosives!
It's fine.
Jesus!
Holy shit!
Alright.
I guess when they impact here, they start moving slow and they trigger the effect.
Pretty damn sick.
I like it.
Let's go to the dark place.
Oh my god, the digging is gonna be uncontrollable with all these energy orbs.
Chaos!
Is what that is.
Oh my god, what a wand!
Guys, is this too much?
Am I going a little too crazy?
It's fun though, you can't deny that.
The fun is here.
It has arrived.
It's a good way to just dig a random chunk...
of level.
Whoa!
I killed a worm, maybe.
What am I standing in?
Feels gloomy.
Ah!
Hello!
I...
I really should put a light on my main wand right now.
But I can't.
I gotta go back to the...
mountain first.
I do wonder if they're gonna send an even stronger...
If I kill this one enough times.
Oh!
Hello!
I see you down there.
Got him.
Seema?
Kinda wanna try some Seema now.
Apparently it's meat.
Finish meat.
Made from honey, I imagine.
Although it is Finnish, it could be made of reindeer blood.
You never know.
Those Finnish people are...
very unpredictable.
Okay.
I'm gonna snatch this!
Yikes!
Also, why am I carrying around this...
tablet there?
I should get rid of that next time I find something I wanna pick up.
Actually, just get rid of it now.
I don't see a use for this.
Is there anything of note in here?
So, here's the thing.
This is a main room.
Right?
Let's try to dig down, west and north.
Let's see how fast I can dig with this new wand here.
Oh wait, the digging's gonna be super unpredictable.
Unless I simply...
Oh, actually it's fine, it's fine.
I just need to get in here and wedge myself so I can't fall backwards.
Like that.
Ah, fuck.
Ah, the recoil makes this really annoying.
I gotta use black holes.
In fact, if I have a recharge...
spell recharge...
I may just...
go grab it and then put an acceleration on the black hole.
And because we have lifetime up...
it's gonna be...
especially amazing.
Hold on, with lifetime up, that's gonna...
that's actually gonna dig...
outside of...
into my desktop.
It's gonna completely exit the game files.
That's how far that black hole's gonna go.
That's gonna be glorious.
And if it goes that far, I only need three.
South, west, north.
Uh oh, I'm actually in trouble.
Whoa!
Grab the blood.
I mean, SEMA.
Don't shoot me.
Also, can I please find some wands?
Just to heal a little bit.
Things may have gone a little too crazy with the wand situation.
I can barely see what's going on when I shoot it.
I guess I shot this one already.
Okay, so what we're gonna do now...
Tell me the spell restore is here.
Fuck!
Uh...
Well, I do have two black holes left.
Maybe that's all I need.
But this... I mean...
Actually, this can just be in here for now, because...
You know?
And... speed up.
I guess we're doing west and north then.
South is gonna wait.
And that's all I wanna change, right?
Yes.
Okay, let's go explore.
Watch this.
Let's see how far it went.
I'm actually really excited.
Oh!
That's it!
What?
Shit!
I thought that was gonna go way further.
Unless it accelerated so much, the game couldn't keep up.
And it started making like the delta time of the game or whatever.
It just skipped through, you know?
Let's try up.
Oh, whoop, wrong button.
No, fuck.
Actually, maybe that's not a bad idea.
Anything here?
Not that I can see.
But then again, I didn't dig very far.
Okay, I had two black holes, that's it.
Let's get out of here.
I'm definitely gonna dig a little further.
To find something.
So, instead of acceleration, I want speed on my black hole.
Did I shoot this one?
I'm not sure I did.
I didn't!
Hey, cool!
Nice little healing there.
That works.
Uh,
it's probably worth to...
store them there.
Nah.
Have one up here, I guess.
Alright, we keep going up.
Unfortunately, I used all my black holes, but didn't I have another way up?
Well, I can just dig.
It's a little messy, but...
It does work.
I just need something that can...
Absorb my recoil.
And I'm golden.
This luminous drill is...
doing work.
It's hard to keep track.
Also, everything is being blackened here, so I almost can't see where I've dug.
Oh my goodness!
Just hanging out there?
Okay, remember when I talked about this?
Let's see if anything's to it.
Okay, there wasn't anything in there.
Alright, well I checked now.
I can... I can go to sleep happy.
Satisfied.
Did I shoot that?
I did not!
Very good.
Now that we're so fast...
I may as well quickly explore.
And dude!
This is what we're doing!
We're grabbing the demon eye and we're coming back down here.
That's it!
That is it!
I have to do the...
Kato dig again.
I'm stuck!
Haha!
All hell breaks loose when you get to the other side.
Alright, dude!
We are back!
Sub himis!
We have made it all the way back here successfully.
What a trip!
Now we gotta find just a little bit more healing.
And then we're gonna go kill Yalki Misty.
Like this right here's healing.
This healing definitely does not scale well.
Later on.
Sup bro?
Sup broski?
How y'all doing?
We also have the boss on the other side of the bridge by the way.
But that thing is so scary because he can polymorph you.
And then it doesn't matter how much HP you have and I am definitely afraid of that.
He's gotta drop something incredible though.
Show me a couple wands please.
I'm flying through this.
What the hell?
What's going on here?
Why do we have spells lying here?
Huh?
Black hole with death trigger!
I'm so confused.
Where did these come from?
I'm guessing it must have been in a chest that got destroyed without me knowing it.
That's the only explanation I have.
The way they are just clumped up like that.
Just be careful here.
Oh wait, water has disappeared right?
Water became something else.
Fuck, I need proper light.
And that doesn't work here for some reason.
Wasn't there also healing in here?
Oh, why is there light down here?
Oh fuck.
No, go!
Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh.
Got it!
Who's the man?
750 HP, I think we have enough to take on this mofo.
Okay.
Let's do it, huh?
Did he get hit by something?
Just be careful here.
That berserkium?
I would love some of that.
In fact, I would love to have a bottle of it.
I'm gonna get rid of my acceleration and grab the berserkium.
Actually, there's probably gonna be more.
There's so much berserkium in this area for some reason.
Just be on the lookout for polymorphism.
Kill them all.
Pea soup.
That's unstable, polymorphine.
That means we're not going there.
Also, is that... I think that's berserkium, so we're gonna empty here.
Wait, what?
Something just reacted violently there.
Now we fill it up again.
There we go.
Just beautiful.
We are jacked to the tits right now.
It's time to fight him.
Oh shit, he's a... that means there's another one.
Oh wait, they're buffing each other.
I need to get them separated.
Oh,
one of them died.
Somehow.
Okay, okay, calm down.
It's gonna be fine.
I'm just so scared of this boss.
He always messes with me.
I see polymorph stuff up there.
I don't like it.
Also down there, fuck that noise.
Where are you, sir?
Show yourself.
I'm freaking ready for you.
There he is.
Come here.
Come here, fucker.
I will show you what pain looks like.
I will show you the pain.
I'm just gonna off-screen shoot him down and hope he loses HP.
Come
on.
Up, up, up, up, up.
There you are.
Okay, he's losing HP.
Get out of there, get out of there.
Make some more persecium.
Careful, careful.
Good, good, good, good, good, good, good.
Back, back, back the other way, back the other way.
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
Wait for him, wait for him.
Ready, go.
He's over here.
Go.
And then we go back.
Yep, one at a time, one at a time.
Bit by bit.
There.
Good.
Get out of the way, get out of the way.
Hide.
Now.
There we go, bitch.
Fucking clean.
What do you say to that, huh?
Fuck yeah.
Amazing.
I'm gonna get rid of some shit now.
He dropped all kinds of stuff for me.
What's all this now?
Fi.
Cast a copy of every projectile type spell in the current wand.
Okay.
Mu.
Every modifier type spell in the current wand is applied to a projectile.
This one.
Cast a copy of the last spell in your wand.
Okay, okay, okay.
Wait, what?
Oh, that's right.
He drops this shit.
I think I accidentally, I dropped this one the last time I got it.
I just, I dropped it, okay?
I dropped it.
It fell out of my hands.
Alpha, cast a copy of the first spell.
If only we had healing now.
Huh?
Okay, so that part of the plan is complete.
I'm too scared to be down here anymore because there's so much polymorphine.
I'm getting the fuck out of here.
Yep.
We are leaving this place.
I'm taking the express highway out of here.
Which means up.
Oh my goodness.
When I actually hit soft ground, I am digging.
We made it to the surface, boys and girls.
Cheers, everybody.
Cheers.
What a Sunday.
Now I gotta get to my HQ.
Oh, no, no, we gotta get the demon eye.
Where is it?
It's right next to the tree.
Should be here then.
There it is!
Get rid of...
I guess berserk you, even though it's kind of sad.
Thanks.
Alright, off we go to coal pits.
Can I dig through this?
Actually, I can.
I'll make a little shortcut.
Actually, that's gonna be a terrible shortcut.
What the...
Why are these guys here?
Sometimes they just happen to be here.
I've noticed that.
I'm gonna leave them there.
I have low FPist in the game.
I don't know what's going on.
It's like my game is not running smoothly.
Maybe I turn down this a little bit.
What quality rendering?
It feels like there's some frame time issues here.
Hold on, let me check if there's something in the back running.
Is it the journal?
Maybe the steam?
Is it the steam overlay again?
I've turned that off, I think.
There's nothing else running.
Maybe it's just a little bit like right now.
Asshole.
What's that?
Oh, steam.
Is the HP lost just now?
Just because of that little toxic shit?
Really annoying.
All right, all right.
So, the plan was to go to fungal caverns now.
And I have no spell recharge, unfortunately.
But, here's what we can do now.
Oh man, we can have infinite all seeing eye.
It just occurred to me that we're back into insane land.
Look!
Incredible.
And let's put on this one.
Let's see how long it lasts.
Significantly longer.
Very nice.
And with this...
The first spell you want, which is that one?
It's off.
Maybe I don't want this, actually.
I like being able to control it just a little bit.
But if I do this...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Just do that.
That works.
What else should I...
Man, I...
Here's the crazy thing.
I can do insane things now.
I need to think on what is possible now, given these amazing spells here.
Guys.
Look what's right next to each other, as if ordained by the gods themselves.
You know what's going to happen.
We don't even need multiple black holes.
Last spell, yeah.
Does that actually work?
It works.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Does it actually work?
I feel like the short range is not working.
There were fishes there, but they didn't do anything.
Oh.
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah, it's working, it's working.
Three thousand.
That's way more than I'm doing with this, I think.
I think it's nice to have a backup wand that does something crazy like that.
So that I at least have different methods of dealing with things.
Wait, what?
Oh, yeah.
What the fuck is going on?
Oh, it's the flammable, weirdy thing.
I also have every modifier type spell, and the current one is applied to a projectile.
Every...
Hmm.
Let me think.
Every projectile type spell.
Damn.
Add some cast delay, though.
Basically, I'm thinking, can I make all seeing eye amazing too, right?
I guess I can.
I just throw this in there.
Oh, it's not a projectile type spell.
Oh, shit.
I see now.
So this would be the one for that.
That's so interesting.
Is this a modifier type spell?
It's not.
It's a utility.
That's okay, that's okay.
Now, this one, we can probably make it better by doing some funny stuff.
Like that.
Does that actually work on this?
Copy of the last spell.
Why is it two now?
It was three before.
I want to give it some...
Oh, you know what I could do.
Yo, dude, dude, dude.
How about we do...
No, wait, that's not... no, no, no.
Nope.
This is fine as it is.
That's actually okay.
If I find a speed, that would be great.
This is my rock wand.
Finally, I have my rock wand.
I want to put a light on this wand instead, by the way, because light is essential.
And put it before that.
Amazing.
And then, I maybe also want to get rid of the energy orb.
It's just, it's causing a lot of mayhem.
Which, you know, could be cool.
But it's not that cool.
This guy is having a bit of a problem there.
That's okay.
Calm down, sir.
What do I put in?
Maybe just a little spark bolt.
There we go.
Probably don't even need three of these, then.
I do.
Alright, that works.
And then the recoil is not as crazy anymore.
Actually, it is kind of crazy, but still.
That's good.
Is this adding a lot of recoil?
Where's my standard spark bolt with trigger?
Did I throw that away?
Why would I do that?
1157.
I mean, that does significantly add more damage.
Look at that, 1800.
Actually, it's kind of similar.
Never mind.
It's kind of similar.
Alright.
So now, let's look at our shit.
Demon eye in...
Right!
Demon eye in fungal caverns.
That's what I'm doing.
Let's go!
Hey, what's up, dudes?
The rock is back in town.
Oh, is that because the air is thick in here or something?
I really need to speed up on that.
I don't want acceleration.
I feel like acceleration is janky as fuck with a black hole.
I want the normal speed.
Hey!
Not that I need that anymore, but...
I'll take it anyway.
Where's the spot?
Here.
Are you ready?
Mushroom three times.
I did that.
Is it pointing up?
Is it an arrow?
Hold up a second.
Jesus!
What?
My life flashed before my eyes.
Jesus Christ.
Okay.
Three eyes.
Maybe I need to get high again for one last time, but I don't have any mushrooms now.
What else could those eyes represent?
Let me read this again.
Also, there's polymorphine falling.
Hardly the place to be right now.
One of my brethren ran away in order to escape our predicament.
They felt our understanding of this world was to be forbidden.
They hid something here in this room, but...
I like the ability to truly see what is here.
Is there something inside of this stone?
By the way, the black hole is the great way to get rid of polymorphine.
It's just gonna suck it in.
Is it, though?
Yeah, it is.
Or is it?
It just seems to pop out again afterwards.
What?
Um...
Fuck me, I don't know.
Let's walk around a bit with the eye.
Also, what's that?
Pheromone.
Acceleration.
Look at the layers there.
I don't know, man.
I could have sworn this would be it.
It's showing a bunch of colors.
Maybe I need to bring the rainbow effect that we find in the hut over here.
If you think about it, that hut was also related to alchemists or whatever, right?
Hmm...
I was so sure this would be it, guys.
I'm fucking heartbroken right now.
I was so sure!
But I guess not, okay.
What's the other thing I wanna do?
Experiment...
I mean, obviously, we have the whole...
These areas over here.
Meat Realm.
Sand cave, overgrown cavern.
Actually, this is the place to go.
To find healing.
Because there's so many wands there.
And now that we have the key, we can just try using it at different places.
I also wanna go back here and grab that radar thingy we found.
So yeah, you know what?
I wanna go back here anyway because I wanna grab the health on top of the pyramid and all of that.
Yeah.
Let's do that.
And maybe even go back up here.
Find that chest again because I'm still convinced we need the key on that chest somehow.
Unless the key is used for a door to gain entrance somewhere.
Let's head this way.
I really wanna go to...
Whoops.
The east again, where I go through the wall.
But there's a bunch of toxic rock.
Or is it cursed?
It's one of those.
I think the only reason I got through that last time was because I had the healing.
I really doubt I'm gonna be able to do that without the healing.
So I will not try and risk that.
I need some type of sustain to get through that.
I really wanna go back there though.
For obvious reasons.
Oh!
That's right!
Water's gone!
Look at the fishes.
It's sad.
They were just swimming in their little pond.
And then came along a wizard.
And he decided to get high.
Not only did he get high once, but he did it at least five times.
And when he got high, he accidentally got rid of all the water.
And these fishes are just stuck here now.
It's so sad.
Also, is the light going out?
What's happening?
That is 100% inspired by Twin Peaks.
That soundtrack right there.
Hoo hoo hoo!
I actually fill up my blood bottle with SEMA.
The desert.
Doesn't the symbol here look a lot like the symbol that appears when we use the Pahasilma inside the fungal caverns?
It's like this mushroomy arrow.
Unless
it simply means, hey, go down to get mushrooms.
Show me the mushrooms.
I wish to see the mushrooms.
Oh wait, I'm just here.
Wait a second, wait a second.
Where?
So I have not arrived at the huge skull yet.
I have been here, so I'm somewhere here.
Oh, but my, I guess my map proportions are fucked then.
I must be... in this region.
Maybe it's saying go really deep.
Fuck it.
Just trust.
Just dig down.
Uh oh.
Oh, all this lava is no good.
Like burning is really taking a lot of my HP right now and I can't heal it back.
It's a big issue.
Suck up all that lava.
What's up guys?
Oh!
Answered question mark.
Wait, what?
Wait a minute.
Is that a mushroom shaped rock?
It is!
Whoops.
What the fuck?
There's nothing in it.
I was expecting something inside of it.
Just keep digging down.
Because it does say arrow down, arrow down, right?
There's gotta be more of this.
Just keep going.
Man, it's insane having infinite black holes.
Whoop.
Oh, whoa, whoa.
Oh no.
Shit.
Whoo!
I don't even know where I am right now.
Oh, I know where I am.
We're fine, we're fine.
Although that's not okay.
Let me just go around it.
I'm on fire.
What is this one again?
Oh shit!
You know what?
Have fun guys.
Wait, why is this not homing?
Hello?
Oh, okay, there we go.
That's a very short range homing.
Super short range.
I don't know, I don't know if I should go down here.
I mean, I think it's definitely saying...
Whoops.
So mushroom down, down.
It's got to be referencing the mushroom I just fucking found right below it.
So there's something with that mushroom.
Like, what's going on here?
Why was there already a hole in here?
You know?
Have fun.
Oh, he died.
So where I am right now is most definitely...
this area.
And if I go down enough, I'm going to get to the meat realm, I'm pretty sure.
But I was going to go to the overgrown cavern, so I'm going to keep doing that.
I just got distracted a little bit.
Go up again, go up again.
Definitely need some healing if we're going to go to the meat realm.
The plan right now is to find healing.
And the way to do that is to go to a place where there's a lot of spells, aka overgrown caverns.
Unless I need to put a mushroom on top of this.
It almost looks like a pedestal, doesn't it?
But why is it pointing down?
That's what I'm...
And the fact that it's two arrows down, and not just one arrow down, makes me think...
Oh, you got to go really deep.
Like, deeper than you think.
Whoa!
The gang is here!
What's up, guys?
SEMA.
Mysterious skull.
Okay, let's go grab the healing up here.
Or the health, I mean.
And there's a boss inside of here, right?
Let's go teach him some manners.
Oh, what?
Oh, right.
Heh.
We're going right away.
Wait, he has to open his face?
Open your face.
Come on.
Oh, shit, he digs.
Did I get him?
Oh, yeah, I got him.
I got him.
And I got health as well.
That's a good want.
That's a really good want.
It's not as good as that, I don't think.
But it does have a lot of slots, and it has spells per cast, one.
Which is super dope.
I just wish that I could edit my ones everywhere, because I'm not going to go back to a fucking HQ now, and...
Oh!
We're translating!
Oh, this is it.
Please!
Let this be big.
Hold on, let me go a little bit over here.
So we have a question mark thingy.
Which is...
Could be an A.
I'm assuming it's capital letters.
Actually...
Yeah, yeah.
And we have the weird four.
Hold on a second.
Could be a B.
Or...
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, and then we have the B.
Do we have the question mark?
Oh yeah, it's V.
V.
Let me make it a bit bigger.
Then I have B, which is...
It is O.
And then the weird U.
Vo.
Vore.
That's one word.
The next is...
E.
Vore again.
Reba.
Rebar.
Rebar?
And J.
Which is...
D.
V.
What?
Rebarred.
I must be getting the first one wrong.
Could be your...
Your retard?
Hold on.
V.
Why
is it not there?
It's got to be the question mark.
Maybe I'm looking wrong.
Hold on.
B, C, D, E, F, G, H, I, J.
I'm actually missing a J.
K, L, M, N, O, P, Q, R, S, T, U.
Actually, I...
It could be a Y.
Your...
Rebarred.
I don't have a Y yet over here.
If we assume that's a Y...
Your...
B.
Hold on.
What is the third one again?
It's the four.
Do we have another one that looks like a four?
Uh...
Not really.
Re...
Renard.
Reward?
Your reward.
That's got to be what that is.
Okay, if we say...
I'm assuming that's what that is.
That means we can add a little bit here.
Y...
Is like a more shapey question mark.
It's a little bit weird.
It's more like...
Like that.
That's Y.
Re...
And that's sort of a W.
The weird four that goes like that.
Actually, it's more like...
Like that.
W.
I'm actually missing W.
That would explain why I'm missing those.
Let's assume that for now.
Let's confirm that later.
I guess that makes sense.
Your reward.
And my reward is this.
One in the... I mean, this is obviously referring to the music.
Obviously.
And you can kick them to make music.
Maybe...
Oh, wait a second.
Maybe I need to do it in this order.
Pond first, then tree, then ledge, then sun.
Oh, am I so stupid?
Hold on.
Is it... is it just that?
Last time I just went from right to left.
Pond.
Tree.
Ledge.
Ledge!
Under the sun.
In the desert.
That's gotta be what that means.
It's in that order.
Okay, that's the next thing I'm gonna try.
So we're gonna do... we're gonna write that here.
Music.
And it is... what was it?
Pond, tree, ledge, sun.
Yeah.
Okay.
That's the next obvious... thing to try.
Like, it's written in that order for a reason, I guess.
All right.
Next.
What is next?
Right, we gotta go to Overgrown Cavern.
And we are kinda half HP, so...
You know.
It could be dangerous.
That place is dangerous.
And remember, when I was there last, I had infinite healing.
So... and even then, it was a little bit, you know, sketchy.
Not really, but you know what I mean.
And where exactly was that on the map?
Below the tower.
Okay.
That's easy enough.
Below the tower.
The watchtower.
Uh...
Let's find a different way in.
Whoo!
Yeah.
That's what I feared.
Let's go on the left side here.
I actually kinda like that it's a little slow here.
Not too fast.
Made it.
And then it's somewhere down here.
Underneath the tower.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Rocks for you.
Rocks for everybody.
What kind of shit are you shooting at?
Look at this!
I'm here.
My map is paying off.
I made it.
At least I'm uh... explosion immune.
In this place, that is big.
Because everything here explodes.
I should have brought my all seeing eye...
for this operation.
Man, the short range homing really does...
not do very well.
Teleportation.
Oh.
Whoop.
Wait, I'm flummoxed?
Oh, I am!
Is it... Oh, it's you!
You little bastard.
I was like, I don't see the effect on me.
That does explain a lot.
Eldritch portals.
By the way, it is possible that I see a wand here, that is just straight up better than the ones I have, but since I don't have Tinka with wands, I don't want to bother picking them up.
I'm too fucking lazy.
I have to go all the way back to an HQ to fix that.
Not happening.
Obviously, if I find healing, then I'm gonna go back, right?
But that's the big one.
But just for the stats, no.
This is a war zone.
And look, wands everywhere.
Just so... oh my goodness.
That's nice, I'm tempted, but keep it.
We're looking for healing.
Even more Admana?
Oh my goodness!
The whole thing is coming down on me.
Massive collapse.
So wait, what was this before?
The vomit.
Acid or something.
I need to play this slow.
Oh, these thingies!
I'm scared of that.
Without healing, that scares me.
Because I don't actually know how much damage they do, because I always just healed through it last time.
Didn't really care.
Now I'm forced to care.
Rotate towards foes.
No.
Holy shit!
Calls the anger of the earth.
I could technically have infinite of that.
If I wanted.
I have so much power at the tip of my finger.
Just waiting to be unleashed.
Nice!
Homing!
That is not short range!
But I can't pick it up, unfortunately.
Not yet.
So is that phlamoxium?
It is.
Nope.
Oh, don't start that.
Don't start that, please.
I still don't understand how that triggers.
Why they keep going again and again and again.
Explosion immunity is helping out a ton here.
Whoa!
Oh, fuck!
What's that?
Shitty wand.
Chainsaws!
Oh, man!
There are so many good things here.
Not what I need, though.
Not my tempo.
Fucking hell, get away from these Poland.
Wait,
I've checked that one already.
I think I've checked that one too.
I'm taking a bit of a random walk here.
Did I check this one over here?
I did, I think.
The hell is that?
Necromancy!
Makes corpses of creatures killed by a projectile rise to your aid.
Huh!
Pretty cool.
By the way, I keep forgetting I can heal with these wands.
I completely forgot about this.
This is the place to heal.
What the fuck is wrong with me?
I just realized.
All these goddamn wands?
Explosive projectile.
Sure.
If there's any place to heal, this is it!
Hahaha!
Look at all these projectiles!
Bouncing around!
That was funny.
I'm a simple man.
I derive pleasure from simple things.
What can I say?
That was a lot.
I mean, this is fun.
In fact, the Magic Guard was really cool when I tried that build.
I imagine you can make it insane with the right items.
Mine wasn't even that great.
It was so slow, the one I had, and still it was super good.
So imagine having almost instantaneous cast on that.
I'm just going for it.
There we go!
There we go, boy!
Now, how do we do this?
I do have a bunch of spells on me that...
like Spiral Arc, that we can probably utilize.
I think I will replace this one.
This is a projectile-type spell.
Hold on, what else do I have?
I have that one.
I would love to not have this one get lost, the Gamma.
Although...
Yeah, I would really... I need to come back here at some point and find this one later on...
to grab this Gamma once more.
That's so important.
Because if I find the other healing, the one that...
the healing AOE, it's actually better, and that is not a projectile.
I don't think, at least.
So...
this right here...
the phi is actually not going to work on that.
It will work on the one I have here, the healing on this wand.
The healing bolt.
But that's about it, I think.
I'm taking that.
I'm going to keep exploring a little bit.
And also...
just heal myself up a bit.
Let's slowly make our way to one of the HQs.
Who knows, maybe we'll find a circle of healing, whatever it's called.
Circle of something.
Circle of...
Circle of health care.
Circle of trust.
What do we have here?
Heal me up.
Wait,
what?
Haha, okay.
I guess the transform there...
makes that one a little bit...
unique.
Oh man, we can freezing gaze as well right now, technically.
With what we've got.
But that's going to take some setting up.
I really want Tinko with wands.
The game is almost unplayable without it, it's that good.
Holy shit, everything is exploding.
At least I'm going through wands quick here.
The cadence is good.
This is the farming.
Okay, deadly heal.
Now that is even better.
Because that heals for a lot.
Thanks.
Even better.
Now we just need the even better version.
The third variant here.
Can we get it?
Looking good so far at least.
Just with the amount of stuff we're finding.
I would say we're on track to finding...
the spell we need here.
Man, my wand is actually really good.
I have a great wand.
I say this all the time, but I feel like this may be my best so far.
It is just doing so much damage.
Giga death cross.
No, thanks.
Not even to heal with.
I can try that.
I am immune.
The thing is, we're finding all these spells here.
So we know if we ever need something like that later on.
We could come back here and just go through everything.
Also, I'm in the wrong spot now.
I need to go back in here.
Whoa, don't go in there.
That's bad, that's bad.
That's very bad.
Back up to this place.
We actually reached the edges of this.
At damage plus again.
Fuck, I wish I could just quickly swap it.
But good to know this here.
Later.
Always for later.
Never for now.
Let me see that.
Check that one already.
I seem to remember this place being bigger.
I mean, one thing is for certain.
We should probably go back now that we have healing.
Just to make something work immediately.
While we can.
Oops.
Oh, nice.
Look at this here.
Another healing.
Or I mean, a heart.
Maybe this place is bigger than I thought.
There's still stuff over here.
Also, someone is confusing me.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
I'm not confused anymore.
Purple glimmer.
What was that?
We're in pheromone.
Now that's a lot of plasma.
Fizzle!
Gives a spell a small probability of short circuiting.
But I guess you reduce castellae and increase projectile speed with this.
Weird.
Let me try it.
Okay, that's all I want to try.
I'm too scared.
Random damage and giant spitter.
Nah.
Not exactly what I need.
Another one of these necromancies.
There's a broken wand there.
But nah.
I've already been here.
Let me go to the right here instead.
In fact, digging up like that is probably a bad practice.
Just because I could dig into some polymorphine.
So if anything, I need to do it at an angle.
You know?
Just so I have a chance to react, if stuff like that happens.
I think that's a general good rules to follow.
Nothing there that I want.
A chest, wasn't it?
Wait, what is in it?
Oh, it was a fire potion, I think.
Jesus Christ, my screen is just filled with projectiles.
Whoops, whoops, whoops.
Concentrated mana.
Oh!
No way!
Maybe I need to get high three times in every one of these biomes.
Or maybe I need to stand on here while I get high.
Okay.
Maybe I need to stand here with this... no, hold on.
Stand here with this thing on.
Or maybe I need to think outside the box.
Maybe it's nothing to do with getting high.
Maybe it's...
No, it's gotta be.
Just look at the colors of the mushroom.
That's totally...
You know.
Hippy.
Getting high colors.
Okay, here's what I... oh, dude, here's what I think.
I think the demon eye serves no purpose other than to reveal this thing right here.
That's what we know so far, right?
What does the demon eye do?
It only reveals certain things.
It doesn't really trigger something.
It reveals things unseen.
And this itself is a puzzle to tell me get high three times.
And maybe I do need to stand on this while doing it.
Maybe I don't even need the demon eye.
Next time I go to a fungal caverns, I'm gonna try and get high and just stand on that thing.
I don't even care about the demon eye.
The demon eye is just there to tell me what to do.
That's the new plan.
And... giant... yeah.
Heal me.
Again.
That's it.
No more.
Once again into the fray.
Dynamize.
Hahaha.
I really love that my spells bounce everywhere.
It makes it...
Also, look at the sign on this wand.
Isn't that cool?
The way it takes a bend.
I like that a lot.
Also, I'm getting a lot of... but you know what?
Getting a lot of money is good.
Because there are places in this game where you need a lot of money and I mean a lot.
So stacking up on that money is a good thing to do.
Yep.
In fact, I kind of want to go up there.
But I don't have enough money yet, so...
Because those things cost, what is it?
$35,000 per when you're up in the clouds.
Those prices are, dare I say it, astronomical.
Lightshot.
Oh, that's really good with the black hole.
That's the black hole stuff we need.
Whenever we come back here for that and even another ad mana.
It's just so many ad manas.
It's wild.
I cannot complain about lack of that, let me tell you.
Oh, here we are.
Forgot I wanted to do this.
Moon radar.
The one below... Wait!
What?
I didn't see this here last time.
This book is new to me.
This is music notes!
G, D sharp, G, E, A, E, C, B, G sharp, F, something.
Hold on.
First of all, picture with the phone.
Picture with the phone.
Got it.
I've got it.
Also, look at the text!
Man, it's really low res though.
This is really low res.
I'm going to do my best though.
Activate!
I don't know why I just said activate.
It just felt right.
Draw.
And here...
We may need some more room by the way.
I'm going to copy all this scribbly script.
Actually, hold on.
This.
And this.
Oh wait, I can only get one at a time.
Cut it.
Paste it into...
an empty spot like here.
This is for the future.
Also, I'm going to purify this later, off stream, and actually...
write some context on where I found these things.
So it's not just random scribblings of a madman.
Although I am a madman, and I'm very random.
Terrible.
Cheers everybody.
Alright, let's get to it.
Now, we've got the F.
Which I believe...
is...
Hold on.
Let me just move this down a bit here.
What's happening?
Oh no.
Things are messed up.
Oh no, I fucked it up here.
That's good enough.
Good enough for me.
There's some kind of bug here, I think.
Tell... wasn't there an F?
The treasure.
Bring the treasure here.
Our reward.
Could be...
I should have taken pictures of those as well, actually.
I should have had the text above it.
It's okay.
We can probably find out the rest if we can't figure out the first.
Alright, let's go, let's go.
So, we have a thingy.
That's an N.
Something goes here that I don't know yet.
N, B.
And that I believe is...
an O.
Let me just double check.
No.
Wait.
And then we have the 4, which is...
B.
B could also be...
W.
Because it's the weird... Oh, this is the low res condensed version.
It's either B...
or W.
I think.
Also, I'm gonna make the text a little...
N, O, B.
It's probably now, isn't it?
Knop doesn't make sense.
It's probably now.
Now...
And I'm actually gonna draw it above right now, so I don't forget.
So, N is this.
Why can't I draw it?
What is it?
It's like...
Like that.
And the O is...
the B...
and the W...
is the 4.
There we go.
So, it says...
The first one is probably a K.
No.
You know?
K?
Probably a K.
And we have a weird wiggly line on a line.
That has to be...
Wait a minute.
Up and then wiggle.
I don't have an up wiggle.
Up wiggle does not exist for me.
Although, it is the condensed form.
It makes it a bit difficult.
I don't know what goes there.
I'm gonna use... I'm gonna make a...
if I don't know what's there.
Actually, just a line.
And then we have the...
square, which is actually the diamond, which is an E.
Don't ask why.
It's just this.
E.
So, it's like this.
Which is actually that, which is super confusing.
That's how it works.
And I'm gonna draw the real one.
Just a rotated square, I guess.
There.
And I guess the one I don't know what is.
I'm just gonna put it up there.
I'm gonna do that for the first one, too.
It's an F.
I know.
Confusing.
Then we have this weird thingy, which is... and G.
It's gotta be knowledge.
Yeah, yeah, look.
It totally spells knowledge.
That's 100% knowledge.
Okay.
Good.
It's okay.
A, B, C, D, E, F, G.
H, I, J, K.
I'm missing the K.
That makes sense.
Knowledge.
So that is like the F.
It's a K.
And W and G is that one, yeah.
It's like the gamma, I guess.
Then we have an E at the end, of course.
Which I know by heart.
I don't even need to look.
It's the square.
Or the diamond, I guess.
Nice.
Knowledge.
And then down below we have a D, which I know.
What is it?
I'm trying not to look.
I don't remember.
It's T.
Okay.
Alright.
And we have the F with the dots on it.
Which I do believe is actually an R with dots.
So that's H.
I don't know why, but that's how it is.
Like that.
And the next one is this weird hook thingy.
The hook thingy.
What is that?
Do I have that?
It's probably... Wait, what?
It's...
I almost can't see it.
Hold on.
What is that?
That one right there.
Oh, you know what?
It's probably...
This one.
That actually looks like that, yeah.
R.
Three something, maybe.
Let's see.
T, H, R.
Oh god.
Then we have a weird...
That's an O.
Throw.
And then a U.
U.
Through!
It's got to be a G next.
It is!
Oh my god, I'm getting ahead of myself.
Oh, is this one?
U is...
That one.
And G...
is the gamma.
It's got to be an H at the end there, right?
It's got to be an H.
Through.
Knowledge.
Through pain, probably.
Also, I need to move my character, but otherwise I can't see.
What's standing over there?
So that's...
Hold on, let me see if I can live translate this, guys.
So this...
This right here is G.
Through...
Ga...
Ga something.
Wait.
Ga something, I'm pretty sure.
Ga...
That one.
What's the last two?
It's this inverted seven thingy.
Inverted seven.
What is that?
It's an I.
Game!
Game?
And a P at the end.
It is!
Knowledge through gain!
Holy shit, I was close!
I said knowledge through pain.
Very cool.
Okay, that's the top part.
Now we get to the bottom part.
Let's see how fast I can do this.
So this is W.
That's the four.
And then we have...
That's the N.
No, it's the I.
With, probably.
And
we have...
Then we have a weird one that I don't really recognize.
Do I have that one?
Could be an arrow, actually.
Yeah, it's probably an arrow.
So that would be S.
Yeah, that makes... Wisdom?
Maybe.
See, W.
And then we did the seven with the thingy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, W.
It's got to be Wisdom.
Now that's an O, I believe.
Let me see M.
What is M?
Is the word S, is that true?
It is true.
Knowledge through gain.
Wisdom through pain?
So, D, F.
Hold on.
Is that the same word?
It is!
The next word is the same.
Wisdom through...
I just looked at the letters.
And the last word is...
Let me see if I can translate it without looking.
So that's an S.
Next one is an A.
I'm not looking at the alphabet.
Oh, and the third one, I don't know.
I'm looking now.
That's the S.
So that's...
Could be an M.
No, oh, no, no.
Yeah, it could be an M.
And then we have...
Oh, that one, what is that?
It's R.
Okay, something's wrong here for sure, but let's just keep going.
Then we have the upside down seven.
That is I.
And...
Then we have the...
I don't know what that is, actually, what the next one is.
Let's take a look.
Is the giraffe that's drinking to the right?
That's what my physics teacher used to say in high school.
So you know you have lambda, right?
He used to say, is the giraffe drinking to the left?
But if you do this, that's the giraffe drinking to the right.
And that's what this one looks like.
Giraffe drinking to the right is, I believe, is an F.
I'm just going to write it up there.
And then inverted seven.
The R is, I believe, what was R?
It was the...
I forgot.
Alright, it's this one.
That one is unsure.
This one, I know.
S, I also know, I think.
S, S, S.
I forgot.
What is the S?
Right, it's the arrow.
That's actually easy.
Okay, F.
And then we have I again.
Because that's another inverted seven.
And now we have the weird thing I don't know what is again.
Which I think is M, but it's not.
I'm just going to write a line instead.
Because the M is going to confuse me.
These ones I don't know what are.
And the last one is E.
What could that be?
It's got to mean sacrifice.
Sacrif... yeah, for sure.
And it makes sense, they're both C's.
Oh, that's C?
Oh, it actually is.
Oh my god, I'm blind.
It is.
Wow, I just wrote it terribly.
Okay.
Very cool.
Knowledge through gain, wisdom through sacrifice.
And you know what?
That is so true.
I have...
Yeah.
Yep.
Also, we can actually get some more stuff out here.
G sharp is exactly what in that language?
It's an X.
That's hashtag.
I'm going to add that to my alphabet later.
Off screen, but I've taken a picture of it.
Also, let me take a picture of it while it's not translated, just to have both.
There, got it.
Okay.
I am taking this one not with me because I have a picture.
We got to go to the tree and try to play a little melody.
We're going to play a little melody.
Just a small melody for the kids.
Something small, something nice.
For the kids, you know.
Large fire bolts.
Feels so weird to be playing again.
Seen that one before.
Okay, it may be time to get out.
I'm going to get out now.
I'm going to fix my wand.
See if I can do that.
And then we're going to try and play a melody.
And on the way out, I'm going to check the wands I see.
So if there's anything, I'll grab it, you know.
Nice.
Let's go.
Let's freaking... I'm so excited about the melody.
Oh my God, I can't wait.
I can't wait.
What's it going to be?
What's going to happen?
Am I going to get a spell?
Am I going to get some lore?
Am I going to fucking die?
Of happiness, probably.
What happened here?
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Did a worm just fall down?
Stop that.
No falling allowed here.
Oh, hold on.
I can just dig my way through here.
Whoa!
Hello.
I'm burning.
Oh yeah, right.
All the water got transformed.
That reminds me, we do have something here as well.
The sacrifice of oneself to the pursuit of knowledge is the highest tribute to the gods.
Fuck yeah.
Love the gods.
I'm doing everything I can to please them.
The gods just get me, you know?
I love the gods.
Not great.
Wait.
Hold on, where's the entrance?
Wait, what?
Am I crazy?
Wait, what the fuck?
Where's the... there was a thing over here.
Am I losing my mind?
Weird.
Maybe I did something to remove it.
Okay, I'm looking at my phone.
I need to see now which ones I needed.
I took the picture.
I need G, D sharp, E and A.
I may have to get rid of some spells.
Put them down neatly here.
We don't need more black holes.
We don't need this either.
We need G.
D sharp.
G we have, E.
A.
E, C.
Wait, C.
Oh my god, it makes sense.
Think about it.
We gained the moon radar.
It's gonna send us up to the sky to get the remainings.
Because we found more nodes in the sky, remember?
G sharp, F.
We don't even have an F.
E, C, B.
G, D sharp, E, A.
At least I can play the first part.
But the last part I can't.
I need C, I need B and F.
I don't have that.
Okay, let me grab a couple of spells.
Oh, I also need the wand, of course.
Oh, but hold on.
I gotta get rid of one then.
I wish I had tinker with wands.
This is just so painful.
Okay, I'm gonna...
Let's go fix up a wand that can heal me first.
Then we come back here after.
Because when that is done, we can start having an empty wand slot.
Or we can start doing all kinds of stuff.
Go down into the HQ.
It's actually not that far away.
It's fine.
Okay, we're at the lab.
I'm thinking spiral arc on this.
Put this here for now.
So I'm also thinking...
We don't need to do anything fancy right now.
Just have that there with a stop sliding.
Oh wait, I can't do that there.
Oh man, it's not very...
Great.
It's really not that great.
We don't even have water to do this in, but I guess we could find a bunch of...
SEMA.
See, this is why I want the other healing spell.
It's just a pain in the ass to do this.
What about if I reduce lifetime?
No, it's too...
No.
Hmm...
Didn't I have something else?
Okay, I can't immediately see an option here.
So what I'm going to do instead...
I'm just going to...
In fact, we only need one of these, technically.
Right?
For later.
I'm going to put the rest here.
Put this one back up here.
We can put this here.
This is my main HQ, I guess.
Do that.
And...
I guess I will leave this...
want here.
I'm going to go grab the...
music player thingy.
Okay, let's go.
I'm going to try the music stuff now then, I guess.
I'll come back to the other stuff later.
I can't quite figure out how to do that just yet.
I may have to go back to...
the overgrown cavern and just really look for that one specific healing.
Or...
I do remember finding some other spell at one of the layers down below that...
I think it was a projectile slowing field or something that could maybe be used.
I think I have that somewhere.
Someplace.
But for now, let's just try this thing.
Ah, here it is.
Alright.
That doesn't work here.
Where exactly is this?
It's right above here.
Okay, good to know.
Back down we go.
Hey guys.
Why are you on my turf?
Explain yourself.
Okay, so...
Let's see the combination.
G, D-sharp.
Fuck, we need two Gs.
Argh, I'm an idiot.
Fuck.
Did we have two Gs at all?
I thought, oh, I already have a G.
Fuck me.
That is such a dumbass move.
Un-fucking-believable.
God, that hurt.
That hurts.
I'm gonna go over here and notice that I don't even have a second G.
I need to go up to the cloud to find the second G, probably.
God damn it, I have a second G.
Fine, fine.
Give it to me.
Hold on, double check the thing.
Do I need twice of something else?
G, D, G, E, A.
We are good.
We're good.
So, one of two things is gonna happen now.
Actually, one of three things.
No, one of two things.
Either, I play this melody, something amazing will happen.
You don't know what yet, but it'll be amazing.
Or, I play the melody, nothing happens.
So those are the two options.
But, if nothing happens, that could just suggest that we need to play the entire thing.
We're missing the bottom part, right?
Let's see here.
Let's take a look.
G, D,
yeah.
And then G, E, A.
Guys, this is it.
It's a nice song, but it doesn't really hit the spot, you know?
We gotta get the rest.
So, I believe I did draw that.
Oh, it's right there.
So, it sits right next to the music player here.
Near the ledge, if my drawing is correct.
I mean, this could be completely off, honestly.
This could be very off.
We'll have to see.
Let's just make place or make room for the notes we need.
I have one, two, three, four, five empty slots.
That should be more than enough.
Yeah, that should be fine.
Let's try and get up there now.
It's also possible we have to play this in a certain spot.
On my way there, I'm gonna try and play it where I found it, you know?
Maybe that's gonna do something.
And we know it's related to the moon somehow.
Actually, we should probably play it on the moon!
That's why there's a moon radar and the text is right there.
Okay, so we have a bunch of options if this doesn't work now.
At least we have avenues to explore.
Up, up.
Quickly try and play it here.
Notice how the moon is directly above us as well right now.
It's gotta be the moon.
But first, we go to the ledge!
To the ledge we go!
Oh, if I hold down the button, it's actually bad, because I flip-flop back and forth.
I need to sort of pause.
Yeah.
Let's just see where I am.
I am above some snow.
Very informative.
Here I am!
Yeah...
Don't eat that.
When I can fly.
Should be somewhere up here.
Yeah, here we go.
Uh-oh.
I believe to the right somewhere, if I remember correctly.
It was free-floating.
Somewhere.
Hopefully not too high up.
Was it off to the right?
Or maybe it's right below the moon at this height.
Fuck.
Okay, hold on.
I gotta go back.
Back to this spot.
Here we are.
Okay, now check the eastern side first here.
I do remember it was somewhere off, isolated from the rest here, because there was no fighting at all there.
It was very serene.
I'm pretty sure it was somewhere off to the right.
Or was it left?
Enter the lake.
Shit.
Whoa!
I'm stunned.
Okay, you know what?
That's getting a little too spicy for me.
Ah, fuck.
You know what?
I'll be back later.
Oh, but hold on.
Is there even a lake?
Water's gone, right?
Oh my god, everything is...
Um...
So I guess the water's gone.
Unfortunately, I still can't breathe down here really well.
Too much steam.
I need the perk now that lets gases ignite around me.
You know, or just dissolve, or whatever it's called.
Kinda just want to fall all the way to the bottom, but I can't breathe.
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
Whee!
How do I do this?
Yeah, it's gonna take me up here.
If I go slow...
I guess I can still breathe, but if I...
I'm scared of dying.
Actually, worst case, I can do this.
Yeah, okay, dude, we're doing this.
We're staying next to the wall.
That's a great fucking idea.
Let's see what's at the bottom.
Man, this really does go deep, huh?
Jesus.
Fishes.
Oh my god, how deep is this?
I'm going to the center of the earth.
There it is.
Oh, hold on.
It goes deeper yet.
Let me breathe.
Actually, this is a nice way to make a little air pocket.
What is going on?
I need to map all this.
Now that looks artificial suddenly.
Oh, dude!
I don't want to destroy the text.
Oh no.
It's one of those essence bullshit.
I'm not taking it.
Also, is this text the same?
Let me just double check here.
That's what we had before.
FPG.
Is it completely the same?
It looks the same.
It's the same text.
Okay, so there's one of these at the bottom here.
There's just secrets everywhere in this game.
So we obviously got to explore west and east of here and all that.
And down from here, we got to go further down.
So what is exactly this right here?
We get a slight angle and then we alternate angles.
I get that pooping feeling right now.
You know, of which I speak.
I'm hyper focused.
Oh!
All right.
That's some lava.
Don't want to go there.
Let's not let these fish suffer.
Okay, so regarding the essences, I think...
So there's multiple of them, right?
And they're all kind of bad for you when you have them on.
I think maybe you have to try and have them all on at the same time and something will happen.
You know what I mean?
Like, you have to go through the trial of going to all of these places, getting all the essences.
And maybe they will combine or something.
And then you can remove them with the essence remover or the essence eater or whatever.
But maybe that will do something, right?
I'm going to write that down, actually.
It's a good idea.
It's actually a good idea.
Get all...
essences...
at once.
Question mark?
Okay.
The next immediate thing I want to do is I want to go up and find those damn...
musical notes.
Even though I'm kind of far away from home.
It's going to be pain to get up here.
But...
Dude, I'm going to do that next time.
I've been playing for a lot.
I got to stop.
It's time to stop!
It simply is time to stop.
Enough is enough!
Man, I felt good!
That was a good session of Noiter.
Exactly what I needed.
Just lovely.
What's up everybody?
I love that emoji cosmic whale.
Looks so cozy.
What an adventure.
Yes!
Indeed.
Is the VOD being recorded to Twitch?
I don't see it there.
It should be on Twitch.
But it's also going to go up on YouTube in glorious 4K quality.
It's much better.
I would wait for that if I were you.
It's going to go up very quick.
Do you want the lame non-spoiler reason for why the statue and the tree is gone?
Does it have anything to do with the game or is it something else?
Is it actually a bug?
Because if it's not related to anything in the game, then you can tell me.
As long as it's not something, you know, if it's outside my control.
If that makes sense.
Okay, something other than the game.
Okay, tell me then.
Yeah.
Feel free to tell me then.
Is it a bug?
The statue on the left side of the tree has been missing since the latest patch.
It was made in memory of the first player who achieved something great in Noiter.
But he wanted the statue to be removed.
Oh, really?
Okay.
I see.
I didn't even notice there was a patch.
But I guess Steam auto-updates all that.
Alright, thanks.
That's actually great to know because I thought I may have done something to make it disappear.
But that wouldn't even make sense because I would still expect the hole to be there, right?
But without the statue, but yeah.
Seeing what he did would be a spoiler though.
Okay.
Yeah, that's fine.
Man, what a stream.
Almost nine hours.
This was so much fun, man.
It was great to play some Noiter once more.
Also, Codoplex subscribed like nine hours ago.
I can't believe that was nine hours ago.
Narf as well.
And Noodleboy.
That was six.
I don't know if you guys are still here.
But thank you so much.
Yujuri, three months.
Amazing.
You guys are really loving that emote, huh?
And Hugonamikron.
Nice name.
I've seen you around quite a lot.
Good to see you.
Are you guys here at all?
Noodleboy?
Hugonamikron?
Not the decrypting parts?
Dude, it's so much fun.
I realize it may not be the most exciting thing to watch, but dude, just getting every letter is so exciting in the moment.
Hugonamikron, what's up?
Thank you for subscribing, man.
I'm glad you enjoyed it.
At least enough to subscribe for it.
That's nice.
Hey, Yujuri.
I mean, the thing that is probably a little annoying is that...
So I can see the text still while I'm translating and you can't, I imagine.
Because of the overlay.
Right?
Do you keep your old game notes in case you made them?
I do, Cosmic Whale.
Mostly, at least.
I think I may have lost some of them for some games, but I'd have to check.
I still have all my notes for Hollow Knight, for example.
In fact, that's even online.
You can check them.
You like the music during the translation parts?
Well, it's from a game called Hollow Knight.
It's a super good game with amazing music.
And there's actually a functional reason for the music to be there during those parts.
It's because I used to always forget to switch the overlay.
So I would keep playing with the map up and people would be going...
Remove the map!
But now, if the music is playing, I know to take it down.
You know?
It's similar to that scene in Inception.
Spoiler alert.
Where they hear this music, you know?
When they need to do the kick and get out.
I'm curious about your setup.
How do you have chat minimized or visible without being able to read?
So the way I have it set up is I have two monitors.
I have the main monitor and then I have a monitor on the side, which is like 90 degrees rotated.
And then I have my OBS there.
And OBS has a little preview of what the stream has.
And on that is the chat, but it's super small.
You know?
So if I look over, if I really focus, I can read it.
But if I look over at a glance, I can quickly see if, for example, people are spamming emotes.
That's pretty much what it is.
But now, while I'm talking to you, I have the full screen on my main monitor.
So I can properly see the chat.
Also so I can look all the way up.
So that's the setup.
Did you resize it yourself?
No, it's just so the preview of the game is a small window in itself, you know?
And remember, the chat is like a small part of that preview.
If that makes sense.
So it's not actually the chat being on that screen.
It's just the preview containing the chat.
It's basically the stream, but in a smaller form.
Yeah.
Oh, and the reason I have it rotated 90 degrees is simply because there's not enough room on my desk to have both monitors at...
I need to have it more wide desk for that.
The rain sounds reminds me of Rainworld.
I know.
Same.
I think rain is so relaxing.
That's why I put it on here.
And in many ways, this game reminds me of Rainworld.
It's just similar feelings you get.
It's one of those games where you're not being guided at all, you know?
You're just being released into this world and the developer says, have fun.
And good fucking luck, you know?
And you're on your own.
You're just out there.
And it's punishing.
It's hard.
But my god, is it rewarding, you know?
And Rainworld is relaxing in many ways.
You get into a weird trance with it.
Relaxing until audio goes demon.
Is the audio bad?
Sometimes it does break.
Oh, hold on a sec.
What's happening here?
Oh, right, right.
Okay, everything's fine.
Okay, so I unfortunately missed the shop closing, but that's okay.
I think I have some food left.
I'm gonna go eat that now.
I'm gonna send you guys off to raid another channel.
Let's see who's streaming Noita right now.
Someone we haven't raided before.
What's this guy called?
I am Hadriel.
Or Sir Petty VG.
Casual Viking.
I like that.
Let's raid the Casual Viking.
Thank you so much for watching, guys.
I really appreciate it.
This has been a blast.
Good to have some Noita back again.
I'll see you in the next, whatever that may be.
Have a good one.
Bye-bye.